
[ 
{
"Question": "What country won the soccer world cup in 2022?",
"Answers" : ["South Africa", "Nigeria", "Brazil", "Argentina"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 3
},

{
"Question": "Who is the first black President of South Africa?",
"Answers" : ["Nelson Mandela", "Jaco Zuma", "Thabo Mbeki", "Cyril Ramaphosa"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 0
},

{
"Question": "How many provinces is in South Africa?",
"Answers" : ["4", "9" "7", "8"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 1
},

{
"Question": "How many official Languages is in South Africa?",
"Answers" : ["2", "5", "11", "22"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 2
}

{
"Question": "Which country hosts the 2014 soccer world cup?",
"Answers" : ["China", "Japan", "Brazil", "Egypt"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 2
},

{
"Question": "Which country will hosts the rugby world cup this year?",
"Answers" : ["France", "Ghana", "Brazil", "Argentina"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 0
},

{
"Question": "Which singer released the song lift me up (Black Panther)?",
"Answers" : ["Chris Brown", "Drake", "Kid Laroi", "Rihanna"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 3
},

{
"Question" : "Kimberley is located in the province?",
"Answers"  : ["Free State", "Cape Town", "Northern Cape","North West"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 2
},

{
"Question" : "What year did Sirena Williams made her debut?",
"Answers"  : ["1995", "1806", "1984", "2001"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 0
},


{
"Question": "What year did Lionel Messi made his debut for Argentina?",
"Answers" : ["2009", "2007", "2005", "2000"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 2
},


{
"Question" : "What is the current Club Lionel Messi plays for?",
"Answers"  : ["Liverpool FC", "Chiefs", "Barcelona", "Inter Miami FC"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 3
},


{
"Question" : "Which author wrote Harry Potter?",
"Answers" : ["J. K.Rowling", "Dan Brown", "William Blake", "Alice Walker"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 0
},


{
"Question" : "What year did Micheal Jackson Died?",
"Answers"  : ["1994", "2009", "1999", "2007"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 1
},


{
"Question" : "How many children does Lionel Messi has?",
"Answers"  : ["7", "5", "1", "3"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 3
},


{
"Question" : "In which continent are Chile, Argentina and Brazil?",
"Answers" : ["North America", "South America", "Europe", "Australasia"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 1
},


{
"Question" : "Which brand of soup featured in one of Andy Warhol’s most famous pop art pieces?",
"Answers" : ["Heinz", "Campbell’s", "Baxters", "Knorr"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 1
},


{
"Questions": "The Mad Hatter and the Cheshire Cat are characters in which famous book?",
"Answers"  : ["Winne-the-Pooh"; "Charlotte's Web", "Charlie and the Chocolate Factory", "Alice in Wonderland"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 3
},


{
"Question" : "What measurement scale is used to determine wind speed?",
"Answers"  : ["Beaufort scale", "Richter scale", "Synoptic scale", "Gusting scale"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 0
}


{
"Question" : "In which city were the 1992 Summer Olympics held?",
"Answers" : ["Atlanta", Barcelona", "Sydney", "Seoul"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 1
},


{
"Questuion" : "What other country, besides the US, uses the US dollar as its official currency?",
"Answers" : ["Ecuador, "Canada", "Mexico", "United Kingdom"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 0
},


{
"Question" : "How many sides does a dodecahedron have?",
"Answers" : ["12", "24", "14", "20"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 0
},


{
"Question" : "The Statue of Liberty was a gift to the United States from which European country?",
"Answers" : ["Belgium", "Germany", "Spain", "France"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 3
},


{
"Question" : "Which traditional Spanish dance originated in Andalusia and is recognised by UNESCO as a heritage of humanity?",
"Answers"  : ["Sardana", "Tango", "Flamenco", "Paso Doble"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 2
},


{
"Question" : "The human body is made up of approximately how much water?",
"Answers"  : ["40%", "50%", "60%", "70%"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 2
},


{
"Questions"  : "Halle Berry was the first woman of African American origin to win the best actress award at the Oscars, but what movie did she win the award for?",
"Answers" : ["Cloud Atlas", "Die Another Day", "X-Men", Monster's Ball"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 3
},


{
"Question" : "What is the world’s fastest species of bird?", 
"Answer"  : ["Golden eagle", "Peregrine falcon", "Frigatebird", "Penguin"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 1
},

{
"Question" : "The Colosseum is a famous historical attraction in which country?",
"Answers" : ["England", "USA", "Italy", "New Zealand"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 2 
},


{
"Question" : "Which animated Disney movie features characters including Rafiki and Zazu?",
"Answers" : ["The Jungle Book", "The Lion King", "Finding Nemo", "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 1
},

{
"Question" : "Which artist famously cut off his own ear?",
"Answers"  : ["Vincent Van Gogh", "Claude Monet", "Salvador Dali", "Pablo Picasso"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 0
},


{
"Question" : "Live and Let Die was the theme for the James Bond film of the same name, but which British band recorded it?",
"Answers" : ["The Clash", "The Who", "The Beatles", "Status Quo"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 2
},


{
"Questions" : "Which female holds the most Wimbledon titles?",
"Answers" : ["Martina Navratilova", "Serena Williams", "Venus Williams", Martina Hingis"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 0
},


{
"Questions" : "Which composer wrote the musical scores for 2000s classics such as Gladiator, Hannibal, Madagascar and Black Hawk Down?",
"Answers" : ["Hans Zimmer", "John Williams", "Danny Elfman", "James Horner"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 0
},


{
"Question" : "Which Danish-Norwegian band released the hit song ‘Barbie Girl’ in 1997?",
"Answers" : ["ABBA", "Aqua", "Vanilla Ice", "Bjork"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 1
},


{
"Questions" : "Mount Rushmore is a popular tourist attraction located in which US state?",
"Answers" : ["California", "Florida", South Dakota", "Texas"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 2
},


{
"Question": "Which planet is known as the Red Planet?",
"Answers" : ["Venus", "Mars", "Jupiter", "Saturn"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 1
},


{
"Question": "What is the chemical symbol for gold?",
"Answers": ["Au", "Ag", "Fe", "Hg"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 0
 },


{
"Question": "What is the capital city of France?",
"Answers" : ["Paris", "London", "Rome", "Madrid"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 0
},


{
"Question": "Which color is a mixture of red and yellow?",
"Answers": ["Green", "Blue", "Orange", "Purple"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 2
 },

{
"Question": "What color is associated with envy or jealousy?",
"Answers": ["Yellow", "Green", "Red", "Blue"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 1
},

{
"Question": "What color is commonly associated with purity and innocence?",
"Answers": ["White", "Black", "Pink", "Brown"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 0
},


{
"Question": "Which color is opposite to blue on the color wheel?",
"Answers": ["Red", "Green", "Yellow", "Purple"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 2
},


{
"Questions": "Which of the following animals is known for its ability to camouflage?",
"Answers": ["Chameleon", "Gorilla", "Hippopotamus", "Penguin"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 0
 },


{
"Question": "Which animal is the largest living mammal?",
"Answers": ["Elephant", "Giraffe", "Blue Whale", "Hippopotamus"],
"Correct_Answer_Index": 2
 },








